{
    "subject": "resource/Dinah_Shore",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1916",
    "human_readable": "Dinah Shore was born in 1916.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.888110339641571,
            "question": "In what year was Dinah Shore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8572493195533752,
            "question": "Where was Dinah Shore born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6747007966041565,
            "question": "What is Dinah Shore's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274844169616699,
            "question": "What is Dinah Shore known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48142150044441223,
            "question": "Was Dinah Shore a singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3340974450111389,
            "question": "Was Dinah Shore married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.275974303483963,
            "question": "Did Dinah Shore act in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24752113223075867,
            "question": "Did Dinah Shore have a radio show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22466936707496643,
            "question": "What decade was Dinah Shore most popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19819118082523346,
            "question": "What type of music did Dinah Shore perform?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dinah Shore was born in 1916.",
            "html": "dbpedia_998_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade was Dinah Shore most popular?",
            "html": "dbpedia_998_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Dinah Shore have a radio show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_998_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Dinah Shore act in films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_998_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_998_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to all five documents, Dinah Shore's birth year is indeed mentioned as 1916."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}